<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jinny Gui&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>https://jg925.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jinny Gui&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 16:56:11 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jg925.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Project Section! &#43; Updates</title>
      <link>https://jg925.github.io/blog/new-project-section/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 16:56:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jg925.github.io/blog/new-project-section/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve now added a project section to the website, accessible here!
Currently, it only has the maze mapping robot project from a course I took at Cornell University in Fall 2019, but it will have 2 more old projects before I add any future projects.
I&amp;rsquo;m also considering writing a blog about why neural network report cards should be mainstream and an industry standard. This topic was inspired by one of the papers that was introduced during a TA lead lecture of the NLP course I took this past fall semester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maze Mapping Robot</title>
      <link>https://jg925.github.io/projects/maze-mapping-robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 13:44:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jg925.github.io/projects/maze-mapping-robot/</guid>
      <description>Description Fall 2019, I took the required course for ECE majors: ECE 3400 Intelligent Physical Systems. This was my first college level robotics course since taking one trimester of robotics at my high school, NCSSM. After filling out a survey for team placement, I was grouped with 3 other students in my lab section, a 3-hour Monday evening lab at 7:30 P.M. We worked very well together as a team of four.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://jg925.github.io/blog/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 17:47:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jg925.github.io/blog/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! Welcome to my new personal website and blog, where I will post updates related to my career goals, life goals, and other interesting thoughts that deserve a special place.
I plan to publish reflections, opinions, and other pieces that I sometimes will choose to cross-post on LinkedIn or Medium.
I started building this site about 2 years ago, and I am SO happy that it is finally setup and finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Intro</title>
      <link>https://jg925.github.io/about/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:06:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jg925.github.io/about/bio/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Jinny Gui, and I am a senior undergrad at Cornell University. I study Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE) and minor in Computer Science (CS). My interests lie within robotics, computer vision, automation, and a general passion for efficiency and social good through a variety of different projects. Although I have done 3 summers of research with the Computer Systems Laboratory, I am now focused on industry and directly impacting the world around me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
